(Penny:)Even if I had slept with him,
so what? Everyone has a past.
(clears throat)
(Penny:)Almost everyone has a past.
(Bernadette:)Come on, look
how pretty you are.
(Bernadette:)I'm sure this isn't
the first girl to hate you.
(Leonard:)It's not.
(Bernadette:)And I'm sure
you can turn it around.
(Penny:)How? You can't force someone
to like you.
AMY:
What if you just
(Amy:)hang around and act
like her friend
(Amy:)until you wear her down?
I mean, next thing you know,
(Amy:)you're in her home,
you're eating her food,
drinking her wine.
(Penny:)No, that won't work.
(Amy:)You're right. Cheers.
(Bernadette:)Oh, I know.
(Bernadette:)Why don't you use
your sales training
(Bernadette:)to go back down there
and sell yourself?
(Howard:)What?
Yeah.
(Bernadette:)But instead of selling a drug,
(Bernadette:)you'd be selling Penny--
it's cute.
(Penny:)It's stupid.
(Bernadette:)Well, maybe people
would like you more
(Bernadette:)if you didn't crap
all over their ideas.
(Amy:)I'm gonna go with
Penny on this one.
(Amy:)Then again, why wouldn't I?
I mean, we go way back.
(Penny:)Oh, my God.
I didn't used to like you.
(Amy:)Shh. Amy's here now.